up welcome to the carnival of influence every mirror lies every smile has teeth
every deal has strings but tonight the cult of psyche pulls back the curtain
they pick escape go paint a target in red name that one instead crowd star
Nobody wants truth when blame them pain
Then they twist your memory, soft hands in your mind
That's not how it happened
Now you're certainty unwind
For consistency, you remember when you doubt yourself
Once they plant this symbol base
You think that what your focus got trained
Then comes brain, or isolation wrapped in land
Your people break you down in phases
Resolving chance and praises
Dependence to your freedom disappears in sight
I swear
I finally see
What I survived
Really think so
Now you're confident
All is safe
Change
Awareness
And once the lantern is lit
Hi, Gotti. How's people far away? Oh my god, my hair. I just did like, I have this beautiful,
I just, a beautiful Russian woman just came over. She came over a few weeks ago. It's my friend,
it's my Russian friends, friend Russia that she met in prison. But, um, gosh, if you went to this
prison, oh my god, it's like, you might as well go to the Playboy Mansion. Yo, good to see you.
I mean, they're gorgeous. I mean, so she came over a few weeks ago and she was like having problems
And I pulled like the death card and I was like I mean it looks like a death
But I never like to say it's a death and stuff well he died and
Kind of like in weird specific ways. And so she just came back tonight to get was a massage. She got she got a tear
We should brought me a few drinks
She has another friend that wants to I know she's another friend that wants because we were getting death in the chariot
And it was and then we got like lies and it's they've been it turns out like he told her that he died in a car accident
He actually unelived himself by shooting himself and stuff. She found out and so
But it's pretty cool like she came over a couple times and then she has another friend that's gonna send me like
You know dinner and stuff to do reading and stuff and so hey, you know wine and taro. Yeah, I have my whole goal reading
I'll still laid out. I need to like putting it away, but let's get some
Oracle's for the chat though, but she the man
I don't know. No, but she's a nice guy with her with long hair like
like they both have accents and stuff.
It says generosity, it says so seeds of kindness.
You know, I'd love for people to be kind.
You know, it's like on that horrible Sandman show,
they're just always just talking shit about me.
Even if I try to be kind and like, you know,
go to somebody's show and like, you know, be civil and stuff.
I mean, the things they say to me are just like terrible.
And it's like, you know, of course, like their own microphones
are all so loud and they're all having big mouths.
And I was kind of.
Maybe not my best. We have beauty dare to be tender and strongly vulnerable
You desire of augmented income. I'm having a good night. Yeah, it's fine
I mean, it's like I'm smoking like a little bit of pot and I know some people don't like when I smoke up
This is my vape and you know, I guess
Some people are kind of mad that I
Vape but it is good for me to get some sleep once in a while. You know and like, you know, so
This is called a mooh-ha
or u-ha
something like that. I've got some exciting news, like the Psychonomicon is...
Pretty much up to date now, you know all all chapters written in the psychonomicon and maybe I'll have to read one one person in the chat
Yeah, isn't it sad you got a I mean, I guess people just hate me now because I mean, it's funny
Like, you know good times and the clumsy also have this person on platform this person no one has a thing to say
But then it's like for me. They'll still call everyone in my chat a horrible name
Horrible slanderous jacket the psychonomicon. Yes, I'll show it to you. It's pretty cool
Can you pull a card for you? Absolutely. Okay, what do I got for you? Okay, Knight of Swords.
This is the Knight of Feathers in this deck. Okay, I don't know. Are you, are you a pilot or
are you not a fly or something? This guy looks like a little pilot, but it's like your brain
definitely is able to fly or able to like, you know, think of like really complex things. I don't
love your engineer or something. What happened between, you can watch Alexander Mayer's
on IRL news time, she covered it.
She had branded an INX on to discuss,
they played the clips about what happened.
That's the easiest way to explain it.
I don't want to go over it over again.
So yeah, I would say watch how she covered it.
And like I said, and like she said,
she's like, we can be friends with whoever we want.
We're going to have some friends in comments,
or some friends on in common.
But we've made a commitment to like,
Just like not bring each other into like these certain worlds, you know, and and respect each other's boundaries in that way
and so I'm gonna be trying to do that as much as I can and
Okay, yeah, this is miss Lola. Hi Lola. What you're sending on me? Hi. Yeah, they say my it means like they keep staying
I'm an animal abuser and all this kind of stuff
It's like I mean it's like it's really irritating because you know when you say things so often
And then there's a lot of new people are coming in and so a lot of people are just thinking. Oh, that's true or whatever like, you know
It's like
Um, a lie told often enough becomes the truth kind of thing. But you think I'm an animal abuser
You don't mean you really you do like what is I don't even know what is considered abusive
But it's like whatever it is. I don't do any of it, you know, it's up goes to the beta
Lola her name is Lola. Yeah, so my hair is not like tied back right now. So it looks a little bad
I'll just put it my
That's better. I don't know if that's the real ghost, but
Here got it. I want you to see this video though, you know, well here. Hey everybody
And then I'll play out some Rungle stuff, like some stuff on Rungle, like that's pretty good, I've been noticed.
It's like a pretty cool stuff, I don't know.
I just really like this video, I think God will like it, or Gotti will like it.
It's one of my, it's kind of like, yeah, here it is, here it is, it's Gotti.
Everybody's talking everybody's selling dreams, but the truth leaks out between the broken seems
The Oracle buffering
Say this
We don't know. We don't know. We busy right now.
I don't want them to be dangerous for their situation.
Okay, fine, fine. Go ahead, Christine.
I don't want to involve in this.
Be done. I I I have to say this and I'm sorry
But yeah, and you can hate me I don't care
Can you please think about this and then do it tonight if you really feel this is what you want to think about what?
exposing fucking Columbia
exposing all this all your all your all your messages beta all my messages clumsy the person that
fucking had a person like make a Wikipedia and goes on around on me like what do you like
pristine what do you want me to think about i just want you to make sure what you're doing
you're okay with okay pristine while you're here and you really want to hear that
Do you really think it is like absolutely okay for somebody like him to sit there and accuse me of shit like that?
I don't feel any of them is any of this is right. I don't feel what they're saying is right
I don't feel
Fucking house
a confetti bomb.
That's evidence.
You know what that is?
I had a confetti bomb.
should not do this until you think about it.
Think about what?
Christine Christine I think you're steaming working with the
I'll be there. I don't even know these people. Come on. And
the beat is not doctrine.
Yeah, but hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold
It's not true. I don't know why
it's not true. I don't know why
but um I can't you want me to talk about a fucking stupid hard ass retarded Canadian drive
please don't tell me what to do i'm not telling you this is my life and you don't know you haven't
known me for that fucking long i didn't tell you what to do i don't i respectfully you don't
But the reason I say that to Christine is just because the reason I even brought it up was because I was shocked when you start saying
Someone's being extorted and someone to put a head out on somebody
Conveniently and conveniently he can't get into his IG
So, he can't find his recipes.
Well, I have all of them.
I'm gonna drop down.
You know what? You know what?
You should have done my love.
It told Summer to calm down
when I'm having my own fucking issues already.
Nothing to do with her.
Rita, don't cry.
Rita, please don't cry.
They don't get it.
They don't fucking know.
Fucking know.
I don't fucking say shit!
I don't want to argue with you!
I'm gonna drop down. I'm dropping down. I'm dropping down. Go ahead and cook. I'm dropping
down. Go ahead and cook.
And anybody see you guys, like it's about fucking coming in.
It's a misunderstanding, Vida.
It's a misunderstanding.
Total misunderstanding.
That's why it's a misunderstanding.
It's about you guys.
Oh my gosh, you f*****g coward.
I was trying to let, that's why I was trying to make Christine understand.
That's why I was trying to make Christine understand, like, this is serious.
Alex is saying that we need to put a hit on her and there's extortion and she's getting
paid for this and she's getting paid for that.
And it's not true.
Come on, Elbow, do better.
It's not true.
You're such a BDI.
He's playing nice guy.
Go ahead, Christine.
She don't mean that
Man, let her talk let her express herself summer did something foul. I'm assuming I don't know and then Christine is you know
Sitting up here trying to I mean be the need to she need to do what she need to do beat it
If you want to expose clumsy the the proof you innocence and just the show, you know what he did
Yeah, that's true. Be look is all right. She has all right to expose clumsy
I would like to completely ignore it
When I was like, you have the fucking proof like beta has proof that it was the other way around and you let Alex
Just run her mouth and say all these terrible things about beta and not say a damn thing
Air traffic control. All right, be the be the you know what the cheer you up be the reading them DMs be the you start reading back
Them DMs and you get back to the program
We need we need this expose a be there. We need this expose a
You know why Christine defending the situation, you know, let me to you know speak, you know
I can't be done, you know, so she it ain't the first time she's shown DMs, you know, so
Yeah, I was the one that brought it up because she sent me the DM. So I
That's why I was like, why don't you tell them the truth?
How I miss VB coming up elbow. I missed that and be people's up there earlier
I'm just a check on be like if she was upset. Yeah, I just like really pissed off because
like my name, my last name, which is like fucking really unique and all that fucking shit is getting
doxxed when other people are worried about pity ass shit and I'm trying to resolve it and tell them
let's work it out so it doesn't fucking get any worse and worse and then people start training
other people and fuck you all because not you guys but nobody gave a fuck about how to resolve
On my fucking panel, Meanwhile, they have their own fucking beef and wha-
This brilliant little device keeps any room ice cold all summer, and toasty warm all winter,
with zero installation, zero ductwork, and zero contractor fees.
It mounts on any wall in under five minutes, cools a full-year square foot room in just four.
Whatever that's going on, I try to help out. Everybody uses me.
I don't fucking need this. I didn't fucking come on this fucking panel to battle fucking
dry and I fucking all this and then like go and fucking like a war with summer and all these
people that don't even you know and just stay away from me because that's why you're getting the
satisfaction of fucking people like Alexander Mayer and psyche laughing at my fucking cry
You don't give a fuck about me
Fucking shit
Bita don't cry. Bita don't no need to cry. Bita
Drama I have to deal with my own. I'm gonna deal with a
Three-year drama with that and that fucking boobies my fucking test post
I don't want I don't want
People but they just appear and they come back when it's convenient for them. They don't give a fucking sheep
because she doesn't get her way
it's not drugs or smth
it's fucking me they keep saying
I'm a fucking pdl
they link me to fucking drug addiction
like all this fucking shit
and you can be like
you only care about yourself
fuck off, please, cordially
I don't need buddy
I'm only here before any of this fucking bullshit
and you can't fucking
say, you know what, Vita, I respect you because I fucking respect people's panel. Don't fucking
neck on the wood. None of you tell the fucking year will fucking end. So much fucking shit
I got in my fucking pocket that has nothing to do with stupid ass fucking psyche and
Whole spiel or any of like Canada try or any of that summer. You guys don't even know the fucking hell
I've been fucking through you don't fucking know. I don't need that do that on your own other fucking platform
Let me deal with my own fucking shit. You understand that?
You know wipe your tears get some cold water get back to make some much a black
You are granting cool ask for your fucking advice or demise all I care about is a little bit in respect of dignity
When you come on my fucking panel, I'm dealing with enough fucking shit not just an
in fucking real life special like fucking person fucking like and like I'm never
gonna be there I don't know why you did wrong with people really what is taking
on me and say you okay don't get people don't cry be there be there there's no
need to cry mama don't cry
I'm trying to figure out what happened. Who screamed that? Who came over and screamed that who?
Are there fucking on ass fucking stuff?
Hey, Samman shut your bitch ass up, man.
Anybody else's fucking panel, it would never fucking entertain us.
They would never entertain us. On my panel, you get to shit on me and tell me how you don't even give me a fucking chance to fucking speak or breathe.
Y'all are fucking ratchet ass fucking like inconsiderate fucking assholes. You never fucking put myself in like you don't even know what I'm dealing with. It's all about you, isn't it? Isn't it?
Disgusting. Disgusting.
It is disgusting.
Get a fucking clue.
Take it on your own fucking panel.
But what I got in my fucking pocket is besides that petty
Psyche is extra. I don't need to talk about
Dango I got so much shit that none of you guys have ever
Maybe it's sometimes
Top 10 or you like B. Do you good?
a little bit the rest of that fucking shit that you guys think is fucking scripted and drama
It's a joke to me. Regurgitate that. We're like just throw it up all over again.
And your name's right. You said that. That's why I'm telling you.
You don't know what your fuck is going on in my fucking life.
You don't know me. Okay?
You don't know me.
Please stay the fuck away cordially go and say how evil I am how bad I am one thing
I'm not gonna do is make sure to view goss about you tonight is where it ends when I fucking go like
Dust I'm done with you. That's what I'm done with you. You talk about me. I will defend myself though
Period so be the what happened with summer though like this summer do some earlier that I miss it like
Beauty was fucking bullshit. She comes up here and search like she has no courtesy. I'm like, that's the thing
I think if I go on our panel
I'm like wait for my turn man, you gotta yell back at summer man with summer
How I do it as I put people backstage
Okay, my boundaries are going to be very quickly scream back at her man. Yeah, I see her turn into a whole demon on the
motherfucking
Shit, you're not gonna do it to me when I'm already dealing with enough shit in my life
Yeah
With her this whole fucking life and this panel would not about summer as in summer come back up
It doesn't mean that she gets to fucking scream over me and fucking scream at me and tell me I'm like this and this and that
I'm on with like 70,000 fucking people attacking me over bullshit and all these people care about is
Canadian dry
Canada dry says something to Christine. I'm trying to like stand up for like Christine
And then here comes summer yelling over no courtesy about what fucking happened. They were showing like tits around
Like all day fucking
Clumsy sitting there and saying I fucking like lie on like fucking
Saying like I'm showing proof and here's like people yappity yapp over what I want to talk about
There's a reason your power bill keeps going up and no one's explaining it
I know you probably try everything to lower your bill
Take out flat flap jacks take out flap jacks and and yes, and you and you all did in her
Take out flap jacks and she that's why she posts your tits beta. Oh
Dead Mark Andy, I know who that guy is. He poured bomb on them.
I'll just put this on and like to go to sleep.
I let my kids run every device they wanted for 30 days.
Sorry guys.
And somehow my electric bill went down.
Here you go.
When legends sleep, evil stirs.
He was the sailor no one saw coming back.
I don't need anybody on my fucking fucking train to like understand where I'm coming from.
But when the seas are ruled by metal and fear,
The sea may rage. The legend lives on. It's time to fight like a sailor.
Every single fucking one of you, the problem started with what?
Cause I had Trisha on my panel, Crystal Marie got mad at me.
Then I had Alexander on my panel, then Trisha and Ah fucking Crystal got mad at me.
Meanwhile, there used to be really, really, really, really good fun with them.
I'm trying to save on my boat.
Fucking, fucking Gemnik doesn't get it.
Now I'm just telling you, just stay in your fucking lane
and you're gonna act like I'm gonna be like this
and this and that.
Stay in your fucking lane and cruise along with the ride.
Don't fucking be triangulating. I don't fuck around with these people's fucking shit
I don't fuck with several people. I don't fuck with Zeya. Okay, number one everybody fucking know that
I don't fuck with Tate. Tate the turtle because she docks me. Period. Those two. That's it.
They need to. I think you and Kate could get along.
I really don't want to.
Can I ask what I did to you tonight?
I just said to people I don't want my votes and I can't carry anymore. And what did I say?
Who are they?
I said I don't fuck with two people
No, I didn't say Trisha
Just pay attention don't make like new narrative like I've never fucking mentioned anything about you or any of that
But you like literally just said mean things about me that you don't remember.
Oh, I'm saying to anybody.
I said things about you or it did come.
You did.
What did I say about you?
You said that I'm not allowed in your boat.
I never said that.
To go swimming my own round.
Wow. Okay, it's your night.
Okay, maybe she heard it and or maybe yeah, yeah
I never said she'll make it go on my vote. I just said I cannot I can't carry
Several people on my fucking shoulder. What they're okay. I never fucking I always I just several times
I said Jim Nick. You're definitely one of them. So I'm gonna go on play victim a little bit more. Okay, she meant
Okay, that's what we'll play a victim a little bit more. All right, okay
It's Jim Nick, please. I definitely most definitely said she was one of them and then she's
Remember, I'm not a stenographer
You don't have to apologize the fucking like don't think it's all about you you don't know the fuck you're talking about I
See people that talk about my fucking family
That docks me
Okay, okay. Yeah, so, okay. I know you're just funny to use to make
No, it's just like a nervous lock there again. Okay
My psyche
Jesus fucking Christ, how do I attract people that either come on me aggressively or it's fucking dip or they think I'm talking about them
So fuck I was even talking about you
The hell? I'm reading the chat, like doing my own fucking thing.
Playing victim and diverting it against you.
Hello?
She thinks like, um, oh my god, I'm one of the coolest in the game.
I'm a Trisha and Crystal Marine.
The fake- the fake people.
I'd like to call them fake people.
Bitch.
Those people have never fucking done shit for you.
Never will.
And go ahead and try bird and try and delete and diverge with them or else. I don't fuck around with fake
That's really easy
I'm like, should I block you so you can go you want me to block you and shoot you like shit
Like you get treated by fucking faded and cracker Donna
I'm not gonna do that to you. I don't think
They completely blocked her
And they treat her like shit and she goes back. So I'm not gonna do that to you. I can't read it
Let's screenshot us
It's really nice having like disgusting people rub off on you Jim Nick
Bad people that talk disgusting well
They have no heart
They have no fucking mercy on their fucking path little anything else
It's really quick to call you a bitch. They call me a bitch.
It's really good to wish death upon you when they fucking wish death upon you.
You are right. I don't even want to fucking talk to you.
Can you just go away?
Go to fucking... what's her name? Trisha?
The best mother in the world?
The best mother in the fucking world?
I would never harm my fucking cat.
little fucking yellow you guys are like you guys just bump together stay away from me
this is my fucking panel yes go away go i've never made a post and ranted about
somebody calling me some disgusting uncle fucker like tisha did
has she ever donated to me i donated to her plenty i sent her gas and her fucking children
With that dirty shit rub off on you. Well fuck with you
the worst the worst
I'm black out to all these people and they gang up together at the end like a hyena and they laugh
You have no mercy on you. Fuck you
Fuck you
Fuck off
You go
Get some fucking help
Do a little bit of dignity have a little bit of fucking loyalty
I don't fucking sit with fucking any of that anymore.
I don't want it.
I don't.
I really don't, really don't.
I never took a penny from any of these people
that talk about me.
They go around to buy me every morning.
They fucking cover me.
They think it's fucking like hilarious
and people that support that.
I just gave them money.
I did.
I really helped them out.
I really did.
You don't see your own comments in the chat. I want to save this live so you can read it
Call me a fucking bitch. How about I pin it again?
Yeah, I called you one early
Alright, so having blackout Andy and like Trisha make fun of me and dox me every day
And you're so scared for your fucking life and you come on my channel and you act like you're a fucking little fucking homey
Is okay with you, right?
Or like having crystal like say that my dad's lecture is okay with you, right?
She didn't know it's okay, right? It's not okay with me. It's not okay with me
And anyone who says that about you, I would fucking put him on the front line.
So don't be fucking too faced and fucking fake.
I don't give a fuck.
You already jumped off before, so why are you back?
Because maybe she had an issue.
I was just trying to make peace right here.
I don't need peace with anybody right now.
This brilliant little device keeps any room ice-cold all summer and toasty warm all winter with zero installation
Zero duck work and zero contractor feet
Sorry guys
Make peace with what you need to make peace with
Maybe
People that make fucking posts about me and jokes about me you just sit there and bow down
I don't need fucking little soldiers like you
I got my own kiddies and guess what?
They're called Muhammad Ali and Miki, okay?
All right mad because you were interactive with
And they're sitting here waiting for me to go to bed like a fucking gangster, okay?
I don't need any of you guys
Fucking be sick as fuck with me
Go over there and let people call me uncle fuckers and make posts about me
Talks my fucking address and your address all down down a little bit more. Okay. It's that easy
I already fucking sank my fucking ship it drowns
Everything you said you make ice cream shut it about me. I will never forget by the way
Well, I have your whole screen recording of this entire video
Everything that is ever done on my fucking platform with 80 fucking viewers is always clever you better recognize okay?
But I got the screenshots of you fucking writing shit
Okay, just keep writing your fucking shit in there. Okay in my fucking chat
Go figure shit out with the friends that you think are like really good parents
Oh my God, sorry.
And people that are great role models
that are gonna make fun of people,
they're gonna put down people,
they're gonna fucking make posts
and like do three or four hour lives,
three days in a fucking robot, people like Trisha,
why don't you go and fucking bow down to bitches like that?
Okay?
It's really easy.
Why do you even care about Trisha?
She talks about me fucking all the time.
Who gives a fuck? That's what fucking people bow down to.
They're scared of that? Get the fuck out of here!
Go! Go support fucking Blackhead Ami. A fucking wax job.
Just fucking doctor.
As people like fucking gymnastics sit silently, act like, oh, I'm so innocent. Fuck y'all.
I don't know what to tell you, but let me have a talk privately. I don't want this to be. Yeah, you guys
I really don't know what to tell you either. I think you do
I think we need to have a private conversation. I don't think we need to have any conversation for a while
I think you need to figure shit out on your own you're gonna be like so vulnerable to
racist people like faded bones cracker down now all these people that like just go ha-ha-ha-ha
every day and they have no content to create on their own except to re-girdrate my content
or make fun of me and I think you should go support that it's really easy.
Let me go take the gym neck privately.
Because I just said, I am a fucking sheep.
I'm not.
You're a sheep.
And you're another one.
Another sheep wants to fucking go.
All right?
Because I'm the wolf.
Bye.
That was easy.
Imagine dancing on people's grave.
Imagine people like making AIs and making people looking like pigs and like, you know, being racist.
I'm not done with that.
Really not.
So I don't care about what goes on between controller
Trisha and their parenting, right? I
I mean, I could and I can have a lot of judgment on that but people have a lot of judgment on me
Meanwhile, I'm just a cat parents, you know, and I think I'm a pretty good cat mom
There's children like villains people talk about me all the time. I haven't I like so these people judge me
Every time I go live, he doesn't trunk. He does this and that
People that are supposed to like actually care and understand me would like not support that shit
Some of my before either go into like 25 more minutes with us. I need like to wake up a little bit
Yeah
I've been doing this cupid and psyche series. This is the one where like, you know
She like her curiosity gets the best of her her sisters have been telling her you have to like find out
he's a monster you have to kill him with a knife and stuff and so she goes like snooping around and uh
Yeah, it's actually reminds me kind of my life a little bit. So let's see actually pretty cool though. Thank you. I like it
A little few things, but yeah, this is my like rough draft
I like to do things several times to get them right and stuff. Thank you very much to say for that
I hope you like that. I do like these uh
Cupid and Psyche series
That's when she like you know goes and she like takes the lamp. Hey, there's Rudy. Hi, rude
I'm having another hard lemonade. I woke up a little bit. It's like a I'm just probably gonna fall asleep
I mean I go through these cycles. Hi, Rudy. Hi, Rudy. Rudy's very sweet
You like to be on my lap all the time now. You kiss a tux and Lenore's over there
Where's tux tux was in tonight like he like see like goes to sleep in the bedroom
And then but I had people over and so he got shy and he like went outside again
But he'll be back tonight probably tux is doing really good. He's really cute. Hi Rudy's really good
Hi, Rudy. Oh, he doesn't have a meow. He doesn't have much of a meow, but he's an old man
Hi
Hi, I heard you try
The text will come back.
The text has been in here every day.
The text comes in, eats, and then he goes,
he was laid behind me now.
He's like, it's really comfortable here.
Yeah, you can be a winner at the game of life.
And they have like the little car,
you like put little pins in the car.
You have babies and stuff and everything's very expensive.
Hi, babe.
Well, I mean, it's like, would you rather,
did I ever win?
I wanted the game of life.
I don't know, I'm not winning right now.
But I don't know, I'll just play a couple more of the videos before I go.
I'll do more on the Keep It In Psyche series.
So this one is, what is this one?
This one is, I think when you shelf the arrow at her.
Or do you want to see the Big Back Kate one?
You can play Big Back Kate.
That's pretty good.
It's not available on the channel anymore.
I'll play the legend of Big Back Kate.
You know, it's a great story.
It's like something to tell your children and stuff, you know?
Let's see. Have you seen it, guys?
Coming soon to theaters near you
Big back cake, the ogre's queen of gossip and hate
She'd call folks laughing cows all day
Then move it, her reflection anyway
Moomoo cake, Moomoo cake
His laughing cow in the state
And dressed in black pimp
So smooth he could sell snow to a penguin in a shack
His hat was made of raven feathers
His boots were crocodile
Wink at it, like to giant back for transportation
If their bear would say she'd run through musts, then she'd do it all again.
She hauled him across valley lakes and creeks, while he sat on her shoulders, eating twelve
rotisserie freaks.
Nobody knows what a rotisserie freak is, and frankly that's okay.
The village scholar studied one and retired the next day.
Kate gave him gold, Kate gave him gems, Kate gave him forty cows.
He gave him an enchanted spoon that only cut him seven hawn-eggans
She bought him thirteen pox, she bought him socks for all his socks and socks
For those socks, socks, ooooh!
Master incarnate, she spent so much on little bear-bear
The kingdom switched to seashells out of despair
Each night she'd host her famous show
The business isn't yours
Where trolls discuss their neighbors' curtains, fences, roofs and doors
They'd analyze a cabbage patch, they'd investigate a shoe
They once debated 17 weeks about a squirrel named Stu
One troll asked, who is Stu? Nobody knew
It would shout you laughing cows at every...
Yes, she'd meet, then she'd accidentally catch herself in a mirror on the street.
She'd gasp and shock, she'd faint outright, she'd yell,
Who is that beast?
The mirror answered, ma'am, that's you, and attendance sharply decreased.
One day, Bear Bear finally left upon a disco yak.
The yak wore roller skates and pearls and never once looked back.
Inside is her tried to help her heal. She ate. Nobody knows why she did that, actually.
That's pretty on brand for Kate. Oh, legend still circulates. She never won Bear Bear's heart,
but she hauled him everywhere from the start. She called folks cow. She spread the tea. She
It's the ghostly echo of Big Back Cape!
MOVE!
The stars were cold
The old prophecy was growing up
It was only beginning
Dumb slept in the-
While moonlight covered stone
And the oryx, no
Soft as summer feels
Bright as a dream
It gathered her-
To your regularly scheduled sleep
Please remain horizontal
Please do not blink. Please do not count the others in your bed
You guys been seeing any of that? Is that off the whole Patrick? You might get the idea. Look at it. It's gonna work at 90 90 degrees
Wow, it's warm. It's been warming warm right now. Let's see if New York City comes up
It's just sometimes they go at the same time
I had to hook it up to like, I didn't do fancy like coding work to do it. Oh, there we go
Yeah, the Guam is hot today. You can go weather 90 we weather New York again. Try it again
But I yeah, I had to like set up the National Weather Center with my like one of my websites
And then like just add chat speed you had to do it
I mean basically it'll tell you how to exactly what to do but you can take quite a while
Call and code helps them that situation too. Oh my gosh
You want lucky numbers
Well, let's look at the numbers here. Okay. We got a spider is number 41
Lucky number 41 guys or do you want? Oh
You but you need a tarot card though. I can do lucky numbers, but I can't do tarot card watch this one
Your tarot card if you want to go on a reading. I'm busy or something like a
tarot card
Spiders that earlier. Yeah, because it is the fool. That's appropriate for me
Nimbus fool there is. Oh
There we go. Whether New York City perfect. There you go
Next to New York is 71 degrees with light rain. The opens are favorable. Oh, there's a high priestess for you Goddy
So, yeah
Yeah, some of the nightbot you can go actually commands and then you can read the whole list
There's like a lot if you want to play around
It is fun. And I kind of like you know, it probably does help the the chat
Out and stuff like that. Oh, there's Rudy. Hi Rudy. You're over here. There's Rudy one of the
terribly abused kittens
They say it's a feral cat colony.
It's not a feral cat colony.
Tux was a little bit feral
because he's just been outside for like a year and a half,
but he's like in a really good shape.
He's like really strong and he's like, you know,
and he's like a little whipper snapper.
He's a little aggressive boy, you know?
But yeah, there's Rooster Rooty.
Rooty is very soft and likes to be pampered
at the stage of his life.
He's like in the little retirement home here,
the little retirement community.
Yeah, you're you want to be on my lap. He likes to be on my lap right now
I can kind of get worried about him sometimes because he has no meow, right?
but
It's very soft used to be a big hunter, but he did catch a mouse recently, right? You got a mouse and
You know with the old days. There you go. You got it again. Goddy. I think that's a sign, right?
Go through the commands guys though. I did the command list come up
Here I'll give you a chance. Look at the commands. No, it's not repeating the same one. There's several programs in there
It's random. I got the fool. So it's like you guys twice in a row. That's saying something
Let me put on another one here
Yeah, I have one kind of based on fluid Mac, but I'll play this one. This one's the idea played the open eye one
But this is a cool one, too. This is a very cinematic. You'll love it here
I keep trying to put on the video
Everybody preaching virtue from a digit
On and selling pieces of your soul in your
It rules disguise the same side always known
Secret chain
The signal bends against the
Vesuv
Don't worry before I could speak
Kingdoms of whispers while calling you
Judgment
But silence while the pressure shakes
Now
It's the story's stress the truth and
Sing game reveals its name
Everybody gotta take names in the air
Like a trial I didn't make by now pick a side prove you one of us funny how fast that support turns to pressure and disgust
I said, I don't know the story. I'm not signing up on claims. You want instant verdicts?
I don't play those games. No paper and I'm asking for more and that's me checking the floor
Are you you were back in me like in the show till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my community
Hey, Stikey, can you pass the music a little bit?
Thank you, bro.
Jesus Christ, bro.
How you doing tonight, bro?
Have you been drinking?
You're really on a good one, huh? Have you been doing drugs? No, not at all. I'm just drinking
But I know what nice so when you see me you're gonna ask me
Have you been drinking and then when I see you have you been doing drugs? Yeah, we got to do better than that
I have a vape I have a weed vape. Yeah, but we can't do that to each other, bro
I could drink if I want to drink
you know what someone got a message from somebody that says hey Chris K is on the show he wants to
move in with you right now oh hey Chris K yeah Chris K has money he said he wants to do chatter
bait with me should I do that oh yeah believe him Chris K does he's a white guy he wants to do that
I was in prison. I was in prison. I was in jail with some peckerwoods before
Do 500 push-ups a day and then I was like I was in the bottom bunk with this one like high-ranking like Aryan
You know grand dragon or something and then he was like
Bring him cigarettes and I'd say I cannot pick up from my little blood my little like sheet. I'd say
Like you this weirdo with my Chinese cat is the most delicate
cat i have this is most delicate i have this is rudie he's an old man amazing oh yeah he looks old
It does look oh, he's a 17 or 18 years old. He's been very soft
You can see his emotions. Yeah, he's not scared of the show. It's a motion
He's really he's a really good cat
He also is like, you know, he was a prolific hunter used to bring rats and then what would you do?
You put them under the pool table in their house and you would you rip them all up to shred
Hey psyche, I have a stream yard right now and signals driving right now through New York say hi to him
Hi stream yard. So it's on your stream yard. Yeah, just say hi to him. He can hear you wait for in sig
Yeah, he's he's door dashing on my screen. Go to door. Can you say hi to him? Please?
Why did he say the n word on my shirt last night like to alexandra? Oh, yeah, he did do that. Oh, yeah
It's too press signal. I must bank them. Okay
This for personal reason
Oh, yeah, you're watching me calling me
Me to pendejo all kinds of words
Good good is here to talk to you tonight. Yeah, I had some Russian woman. I just got out of prison recently
You want to see my cat with a dress yeah
But they're her.
Aw.
You guys, dress is like being patriots, yeah.
They're always in outfits.
the two twos and so. Oh, it's
a biker jacket. Oh, she's is
that a prison? She sleeps on
my expensive as PC. Oh, on
your on your computer. Well,
it's keeps her warm. Is it
warm? Yeah. Yeah, she's she's
on the leash because she likes
going out. We just came back.
Hey, psyche. Yeah, I'm horny.
Okay, come on over. Come on
I know where you're at psyche. We're gonna make it happen one day and just have fun
over guys. It's like anything.
Let's not plan it because if you plan it, it's weird. Yeah, yeah, but I'll see you that's weird
Tomorrow morning. I want you to wake me up with some coffee and uh
You know a McRiddle no signal left because he doesn't approve of our relationship. Oh, well, he's a little bitch
You know, I saw his
Like you're nice
Big dick, you know, but he was trying to do a helicopter with they got with like a popsicle stick
I mean, yeah, you saw his dick. Oh
Several times
Oh you saw it hard
No, it's like dark.
What's dark?
Yeah.
Have you ever seen the Hispanic guy?
Some of them have a black dick.
It's like really weird.
Do you have a darker one or do you have like a lighter?
I have that uncut, dark skin.
Oh my gosh.
You're a black uncut dick.
Okay.
Okay, I'm interested in seeing that. I mean, it's just for personal
You don't have to have to buy me a stuff cross piece
You showed it you just show before my show because I have a video do you remember this video?
I mean, it's they I shouldn't put it on it
But it's a view and say harassing me and putting your dicks on the screen. I have it's on roll. Yeah. Yeah
Do you want to see it? You're on you're actually on it. I don't want to see it. No
All right, let's see it there running back
I mean, yeah, and I say some nice things about your cleaners. I think you're in the you're in the thumbnail, too
I'll show you. It's pretty good. Yeah, you're gonna get your YouTube band. I'm not gonna be too bad
It hasn't been banned yet after all I'm a rumble. So I don't care. I showed my dick. I was drunk. I don't care
Show your dick on this. It's just gonna. Oh well it happened, bro
I can't change what I did when I was drunk
You see they look down there check out the thumbnail or check out the thumbnail of the video here
It is don't show kicks. You see it. You see it. I mean I think they're leaving our dicks
Right on the right side. Thank you. Oh
signal
All of the is that is that one? Yeah, it's a busy gate. It's busy gate. So we'll check it out
You're on this video you're on rumble on another channel
You're on my channel, but what the fuck?
Did what happen?
When I say show this little PB. How long ago did it happen because I'm just coming out of the ring
I can't really hear it. Okay. I got it. I got it's volume home sick show this PP about
Oh, that's because he had my volume on zero of Arthur. That's why you couldn't hear me because but now it's on 200
So, oh my god, I'll just run in a mouse Lola run in a mouse. How long did it take for that? Oh my god the rage to end
Great, you can't fuck it! You don't have skimpers!
For that, you don't have skimpers!
What did you just say about me though? My anti-gay, my anti-social?
Do I just go into a rage when I say a cock?
Like, well, I don't know. What does that say about me?
You're anti-porn bomb. You're anti-porn bomb.
You are anti-powder
I've sat on panel with for a long time on other channels
You know I'm saying that fuck with me bro, but you know what? I want that to be like a little weird. I should not be hit
Let him on because you all gonna let him on dick. So I gotta face the fact
because you like that shit, whatever. I'm not gonna tell you, not to, not let on, but now I'm laughing at it, man, but ooh, ooh, but, you're mad, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're,
I was not so mad, you're so mad that I had your mic at zero for like 20 minutes, you even noticed
Yeah I know, I noticed it after, I watched, I'm like yo, bro this, they didn't hear a word, and good because I was
What are you talking about, psyche, I don't see nothing, I swear it is
I heard you talk, that's not fucking, I wouldn't
You don't see it
Box in their kitchen. We're gonna little pee pee and you laugh
Again, and you laugh and you let them up again the next day and they pull their dick
People judge
When you make fun of it, my fun is deflect.
You'll keep letting these people on this
Go send some more money pussy
No, you didn't need to send me money, just, just, um...
Nah, you hungry, tell him, tell him, baby, I'm hungry.
You're crazy.
Alex, you're not getting back on until I get my McRiddle.
Fuck.
It's perfect. I love it. Yeah.
That rule stands. Until I get my McRiddle,
I just went through it fast.
You're making stuff up, dude.
Awesome. I have food. I actually have some tacos.
I have some Mexican food in the freezer.
Hey, they have Mexican taco.
I eat a big Mexican taco.
I'll go in and breathe.
Oh, yeah, we know what's up.
Coladas with the olives.
I want the olives in it.
I went to a lot of sauce.
I want the fructias.
Saiki wants to be the middle of a 300 glow and squid sandwich.
Oh, do you like Squidward?
He might be an R3.
Nah, me and Squidward don't get along.
But I kind of like we have hate sex with me.
You know what's.
Hey, Saiki, if I ever go to your house, let me cook.
Okay
Yes
Like the cousin I hate that's what
Yeah, screw is a pussy he'll just he's the cousin they'll blame you for everything you know, he can't take liability or
Yeah
I
Okay, he hasn't been he hasn't even been live he hasn't joined nobody's stream no more
I think he ended up dying R.D.
Well, I saw you was like at like something like duck pond
Like and like he was like, you know, but the water for me and then then his camera kept cutting out
So that was very important. I think he's dead
He died? Oh, no. But then I thought KZ died. I was so excited and then he would turn out to be alive
Well, that's not my fault. People die, bro
To come back to life in this community
I don't know. So, 300, I'm going to look at your entry in the psychonomicon again. I think I got the Oracle working for me. So, I'm going to look at 300 loads.
Oh, yeah. Because remember, it's like all this stuff.
Hey, hey, psyche. Look me up. Follow me on rumble. You don't have a rumble?
I will. I have a rumble. It's up in right now. Hold on.
Alright, let's read my AI.
Yeah. The Oracle does it.
From my chat.
Yeah.
I was having 12 viewers today. A lot of 12 viewers, my most.
Hold on, it's working.
Hold on, it says 300 glow.
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
I was gonna say, oh, so it's no content.
Okay, so maybe I got a different,
so maybe it's just 300 glow, GLO,
because I did it all authentically, okay?
Hold on, let's see if it works for that,
300 glow.
The archive holds, so record of this,
okay, now I have to look at the O4.
I know you're in here, 300.
Yeah, there you are, see, 300 glow.
Oh yeah.
It says, your former guest has himself on stream alongside SIG, and it says,
Sirene Glow appears in the archive as a mentioned former guest whose primary
documented action is participating in an on-stream exposure alongside another guest named SIG.
He represents a category of a guest who's engaged man with the show,
crossed into behavioral territory that generated friction and administrative response from the host.
The solo substantive record of 300 Glow's presence in the archive occurs within the context of episode 408,
where his actions are referenced as part of a broader pattern of guest misconduct
that the host psyche is actively managing. His appearance or rather his exposure functions as
narrative for the episodes of opening tension. It also mentioned alongside similar behavior from
I require those attention and comment. The incident appears to have been public enough to warrant
framing within this episode structure, suggesting the exposure was visible to the audience rather than
a private matter. I know, I said if you're going to do it, just do it privately backstage. It's
the A.I. knows what I was doing, that's what I'm talking about, I'm talking about your wiener, and I said, yeah, and then you're in this episode of the stupidity is painful, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know,
in there and I'm like he just died literally I don't think his body is
the perfectly cold yet and she's like making fun of me they're like oh well
you're making fun of the dead they're making fun of the dead they're calling
also Michael the piece of shit and stuff I mean there's sick people there's sick
people I never said horrible things like these about these people like they're
saying I mean they're sick
Let me get to you really pull your dick out like
This is the only one that really has pull this dick show. I missed some of it. So here's
You can see my hair is getting a little bit wild
Ain't no dick getting pulled out
Three sheets the wind is three sheets to the wind last night. I'll show a little bit of my girls like trying to see
Okay, oh shit
You wanna see some? Here we go guys, this is last time.
Crystal Marie here with Clancy and Jamie.
Fuck you over. Even your boy did. Thank you.
I don't even know how many boys your prison night fuck you over.
Aldi, right? You gotta say because my boy's Aldi. That's why.
Hey, Crystal Marie, you cannot be mad at Aldi because he didn't want nothing to do with you.
Oh my gosh, she was harassing me! Haven't you seen how I...
Please stop!
It's the oil!
That's weird shit to me!
You're a weirdo, too!
You guys are weird, dude!
I'm weird. I'm weird.
You guys need to figure out life.
Okay, because that was just a little fucking, that was just a little dare I had, okay.
Yeah, you want to tag kids you wrote that in the DM to be to why make it again. Why don't you call the cops nigga? I don't need to call the cops. You're the weirdo nigga. Go ahead. Let's go cook it up.
So Jamie what you want so Jamie so Jamie on his answer, right? Jamie you want to dance her back in a female though?
I did that about Jamie. I'm talking. I didn't lose a female. I didn't know you a female
I don't know. I don't know. I
You just don't need to pay attention to you right now, right? Where are you?
He left?
Well, I was gonna just
Okay
Well, let's go back to the rumble thing. I'm gonna be a cry for another hour
I mean having some taquitos, but I just ate one it was half frozen. It's not the best taste in the world
Okay, let's see. Where are we? Oh
Trif kick
I can play like, you know, like fights and stuff. I'm not the Chris K, like Midge's thing. Chris K, if you're here.
I want to talk about the Cheddar Bates rules.
Chick and the Whooped by Bear is, hey, so the guy named Fuzzy Bear, like it's like a random name, Fuzzy Bear.
So I know it's like, you know, Aldi. So I told Goodtown that I was like, hey, Fuzzy Bear is in your chat.
And I got the Aldi, he's like, it's not Aldi, but it's a Crystal Anne, Carterverse meets the Pannaverse.
This is, I guess, that monumental episode.
Hello hi hi
I just happen to see clumsy in the chat and I would love to confront him if he's willing to take the link because he has a
Lot of shit to save me on my back. So like I said same thing that happened to you that I confronted you about and
Kate just now, you know
Yeah, and he's see he's like attacking and chat. Why do you have first of all? I don't know you clumsy
I've only heard of you because of one person and that same person
keeps
going at. Oh, yeah. Let's see.
There we go again. But, wow.
Can you come up here and talk
to Chris? You know, she's a
really reasonable person. She's
like a nice person. Oh, I think
he's like he's the last person
I need to confront, too, because
I noticed he spoke to me like
few months ago and
he's like he's like he's
But and his DM to this other person. He said it was because I was on beaters panel. Okay. He's here to talk to you here to talk to you
like he's like he's like he's
What's up?
Let me explain myself. Let me talk first. Okay. Okay, and then hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on bitch
I don't even know you know, bitch. They don't you're gonna listen to me, bitch
You're gonna listen to me
Shot out to gamble
Yeah, I have no issues with
you. Yeah, but he exposed you.
That's how I know about it.
Yes, he did.
No, he was he told me about your
plastic little baby.
We're not plastic baby.
You don't know plastic baby.
So I think they're talking.
Let us talk.
OK, let her have her opinion.
Well, I'm still talking.
I'm still talking.
Shut up, Crystal.
And no, shut up.
Shut up.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're not gonna tell me to shut up. Shut up, bitch. I was here first. Shut up. I had to be very respectful. Shut up. Oh, clumsy, clumsy, clumsy. Let me just say what I have to say. Okay, okay, okay, okay, letter. Oh my God.
The DM said, you were stringing me because that I was on Vita's life. Here's the thing, do you know I met Vita real life?
I'm captain content right now both suckers did
Wait, you want me to answer a question, hold on hold on you and be to know each other because y'all fuck captain content, right?
You remember you
Made you crash the fuck out Gucci's made you fucking leave the RV
uh no yes you did i left on my own and where are you because you couldn't handle it you
couldn't handle it you got kicked out you got kicked out by what you kept from content
let clumsy i don't know you at all i don't know you you little bitch don't even i know you because
a gamble
are obsessed with my past from what, three years ago?
Four years ago?
That's embarrassing.
I'm, I'm, honestly, honestly.
Oh, I'm upset.
And you think it's cool for families
to get, you think it's okay to have people get
with families who love people.
Let me talk.
Why don't you leave Ianex alone then?
No, she will arrest my family.
You dumb fuck show proof. I have the proof, but I'm not
Clumsy I nx is no for contacting the family members and stuff. Oh, I'm gonna go get drinks
Just like everyone else like he's just like everyone else around here. Why let me talk God
Sorry, shut the fuck up, bitch
Are you her mouth? Maybe you should shut the fuck up, bitch
Yeah, like for real
No one likes I don't give a fuck about you crystal and okay the reason the reason your bitch
Has got brought up because I and nix came up talking about you
You stupid
Guess what guess what that sounds like you and her problem not me you bitch
but it's fine but when don't try to attack someone that knows you're fucking war okay can salmon come up here to protect me
no because salmon has a freaking brain
okay guys thank you for being here i'll see you later okay